<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Contents>
<page src="start" title="Library"><![CDATA[Library Library  The Library provides you with the learning content for selection and viewing purposes. It is the interface between the author and the learner.It provides an overview of the available groups and simulations, books and book pages. Selecting a simulation displays the associated modes and documents. You can work through the structure created in the Library by the author or select specific learning content. A search and filter function makes it possible to search the content, allowing specific topics to be found quickly and easily. To be able to work effectively with the Library, you need to understand how it is organized and what functionality it has. The following sections will provide you with the necessary information on how to work with the Library. The Library, Trainer and Book Reader are web-based applications and are therefore launched in the browser. Before you start to work through the learning content, ensure that the  necessary settings  (Link->cdoc!CD_BD6527EAA3F6F194.htm) are available in your browser. This will avoid errors in the way the learning content is displayed and runs. Consult your administrator if so required.   Note: Bear in mind that this Help function describes the Library's standard functions. These are not necessarily also displayed in your Library. The Library's appearance and functions depend on the author's settings and may vary as a result.   ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_B8E8BCDBBD7A2B7" title="Library Architecture and Components
"><![CDATA[Library Architecture and Components
 Library Architecture and Components   The Library is broken down into the following two main areas: the course structure on the left-hand side and the view of the selected content on the right-hand side. The areas are separated by the central bar.   Library components and their functions    Header:The caption of the current selected item is displayed in the header. It also contains these control buttons:     Previous: go back to previous or superordinate item in course structure.    Next: go further to next or subordinated item in course structure.    Help: open help for according functionality    Settings: display the settings dialog to adjust your personal settings for search and Library behavior. It also enables you to access the help for each function.    Close: close Library window.     Search area:     Enter a search phrase to be searched for within all items shown in course structure. You can adjust which item parts to be searched within the settings dialog.    Open the dropdown menu to go to the views for Favorites, Page History and Glossary.     Course structure:The course structure displays the learning content of the course and allows this content to be selected. When you use the search function, it will display the appropriate matches to you.    Central bar:The central bar separates the course structure and the view of the learning content. It enables you to alter the size of both areas by dragging the centrally located button.    Navigation path:This bar provides you with breadcrumbs to navigate more easy through content levels. As well you find here the Favorite status. Just click the star symbol to add or remove current Library page to/from your favorites list.    Mode overview:When selecting an item in course structure, the associated playback modes are laid out in this area as buttons that can be clicked to launch the specific mode.    Learning content description:For any selected item in course structure, this area shows corresponding descriptions providing you with additional information.    Asset overview:When selecting an item in course structure, all associated assets like documents or videos are shown as links within this area. If available, item links appear with type icons identifying known asset types.    ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_48C000DF67102D91" title="Course Structure"><![CDATA[Course Structure Course Structure  The course structure organizes the available contents. It allows you to select learning content and, using the search, it will display the corresponding results. Course structure architecture The first level of the course structure specifies the main directory containing the content. Clicking on the preceding arrow icon expands or collapses each list item. The associated learning content can then be seen and selected. Selecting a learning content displays its content, modes and assets within the right-sided overview area. Course structure content The following content can be displayed and launched in the course structure.   SimulationsWhen a simulations is selected, the associated modes and assets are displayed in the overview, enabling you to start or download them.    BooksWhen selecting a book, a button is displayed in the overview to start the Book Reader functionality.    The content displayed in the Library depends on the materials provided by the author. ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_41F667D795DEE0B7" title="Search"><![CDATA[Search Search  The search function makes it possible to pinpoint learning content on a specific topic area. The learning content descriptions, search terms and titles can be searched.The search is arranged under the course structure. Searching in the course structure This is how you can search learning content:   Enter a search text or term in the text box.    Then select the criteria on which you would like to search the Library content. The corresponding settings can be shown using the more... button.     Search description:If this setting is activated, the text descriptions accompanying the learning content are searched.    Search title:If this setting is activated, the learning content titles are searched.    Search keywords:If this setting is activated, the keywords defined by the author and assigned to the learning content are searched.       Then click on the Search button.    Any learning content found is displayed in the course structure and the other objects are hidden. Clicking on a title selects the corresponding object. Clicking on the preceding shortcut icon selects the object, which is also displayed at the appropriate position within the course structure. Removing the search results To remove the search results, click on the Delete search results button next to the search. This will restore the original state of the course structure. ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_EC77954C8B73B392" title="Selecting the Content of a Simulation"><![CDATA[Selecting the Content of a Simulation Selecting the Content of a Simulation  Selecting a simulation in the course structure displays buttons on the right-hand side for calling the associated modes and documents or, in the case of a book, a button for calling the book. Integrated documentsThe documents belonging to a simulation are displayed in the lower row. These can be Word, PDF or HTML documents, for example, as well as audio, video or photo files. When a document is selected, it is displayed in the relevant program. Simulation modesThe modes belonging to a simulation are displayed in the topmost row. A simulation can contain up to four modes, fulfilling different learning goals.   Demo modeThe mode allows a process to be watched and followed. Each step is explained with descriptions corresponding to each action.A navigation bar is displayed for controlling the mode.    Practice modeInstructions allow you to interact with a simulation, perform actions and processes by yourself and thereby understand them.    Test modeIn test mode you can run through a simulation on your own and without supporting explanations. This serves to inwardly digest and test one's existing knowledge. When you perform an action, you receive confirmation whether it was performed correctly. At the end of the mode, you are shown the result of how many of the actions were performed correctly.    Concurrent modeConcurrent mode can be used in parallel with working with an application and helps you as the process unfolds. You are shown step by step in a window the course of events, which can be individually controlled. This allows you to comprehend what is going on and perform these actions in the actual application.    Descriptions You will find a description and other information about the learning content you have selected beneath the simulation selection button. This information can give you an idea, for example, of what the simulation is about, what the objective is of the process in question or what prior knowledge is required. ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_88210301367B3C8C" title="Starting a Mode"><![CDATA[Starting a Mode Starting a Mode  The displayed buttons allow you to start the mode of your choice. The playback takes place in the Trainer, which is opened in line with your settings.  View settings Before starting a mode, you can define the view in which it is to be opened:   In a new windowIf this setting is activated, a mode is opened in a new window.If the setting is deactivated, the simulation will be opened in the Library browser window. Be aware here as well of the Leave course structure open option.    If you have applied settings in your Library, these will be retained even after the Library has been closed. That means that you can keep them as your default settings and do not need to reapply them when you next launch the Library. Start mode To start a mode, click on the corresponding button. The mode of your choice will then be opened and played back in the Trainer. When playing back a simulation, an individual start page will be displayed for each mode. This page will contain an explanation of the mode and the user will receive an introduction to the application and way in which the mode operates.Now click on Start. Depending on the mode you have selected, you can now run through the simulation or play it back. If the simulation has been completed or terminated prematurely, the Trainer will indicate as much by means of a stop page. In Test mode the stop page will indicate whether you have passed the mode as well as an assessment of the result you achieved.   Note:  Should the required browser settings for playing back a simulation not be correct, this will be indicated by an error message. You can now change the browser settings and restart the mode. Please also refer to the Browser Settings section. Please bear in mind that start and stop pages are not necessarily displayed. The author can deactivate them. This will cause a simulation to start and close automatically.    ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_D3ED30040166409F" title="Books and Book Pages"><![CDATA[Books and Book Pages Books and Book Pages  When selecting a book, a button for starting the Book Reader appears in the learning content overview. Depending on your settings, the book will be opened either in a new window or the same one. Close the Book Reader if you would like to return to the Library. You can scroll through the book pages in the Book Reader as well as start and look at the objects filed in the book pages. Please refer here to the Help function in the Book Reader. Displaying a book page If a book page is not assigned to a book, then the page will be displayed, after it has been selected, directly in the learning content view in the course structure.  You can then hide the course structure if you only wish the book page to be displayed. The central bar can be used to show the course structure again so that additional learning content can be selected. Opening modes and documents from a book page As with the Library, learning content is also started in the corresponding programs. That means that when selecting a mode, the Trainer is started, whereas when selecting a document it is the corresponding program with which the document can be displayed that is opened. ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_9ABC72A61D06B6A1" title="Opening Documents"><![CDATA[Opening Documents Opening Documents  If you select a document, it will be opened directly in the associated program in an external browser window. You can now view it and work through it or save it individually on your drive or data medium. The document formats can be very diverse, for example in Word or PowerPoint format. That means that you should have Microsoft Office or a comparable product installed on your workstation to view the documents. If there are any documents in PDF format, these will require a PDF reader. Please refer if necessary to your administrator if you require such a program. ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_153843B1A98D5B83" title="Trainer"><![CDATA[Trainer Trainer  The Trainer is the functionality for playing back a simulation's different modes. A distinction is made here between the following modes:   Demo mode    Practice mode    Test mode    Concurrent mode    Demo mode provides you with the means to control the Trainer. This allows you individually to control the playback of the mode as well as apply settings for the Trainer bar and audio content. In practice and test mode the bar is not displayed so as to prevent the user from manipulating the sequence of events as the user interacts with the content. The concurrent mode is displayed in a window with a control which resembles the Trainer interface in demo mode in terms of its functionality. This makes it possible to call individual actions and process sections. You will find additional information on this subject in the section on the top-most window. The following sections provide you with an overview of the functions of the Trainer bar and their application so as to make it easier for you to work with the Trainer. There is also an explanation of the top-most window for concurrent mode. The Trainer is a web-based application and is therefore started in the browser. Before you start playing back the modes, ensure that the necessary settings are available in your browser. This will avoid errors in the way the modes are displayed and run. Consult your administrator if so required.  ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_7A7C3E006F8DA196" title="Trainer Bar Architecture and Components
"><![CDATA[Trainer Bar Architecture and Components
 Trainer Bar Architecture and Components   The following functions are available to you in the Trainer bar. The components listed below therefore represent the Trainer's basic functionality.    Orientation This function allows to position the Trainer bar optionally at the bottom of screen or at the top.    ControlThese buttons allow the way a simulation unfolds to be individually controlled.    Text This button enables you to set quickly if text bubbles shall be displayed or hidden.    AudioThis button enables you to switch quickly between audio playback and silent mode. It only appears in simulations with audio enabled contents.    VolumeThis function allows you to control or deactivate audio file volume and bubble effects. Clicking on the button opens a selection menu from which the volume can be controlled and the sound deactivated by means of a selection field. It only appears in simulations with audio enabled contents.    Progress display The progress display provides an overview of the steps and displays how the simulation is progressing. Among other information, it displays the title of the chosen simulation and name of the step currently being presented.    Help This button displays the help of Trainer functionality.    Close The Close button terminates the mode and the Trainer is closed.    ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_2453F82EC484D5BE" title="Control buttons"><![CDATA[Control buttons Control buttons  The mode control buttons are arranged on the left-hand side of the Trainer bar. They offer you the following functionality:   Previous / NextThe buttons allow you to jump to a previous or following step.Alternatively, you have the option of selecting a step via the progress display.    Pause / Continue The Pause button pauses the simulation. If the function is activated, the button switches to Continue.The function of the Continue button, if pause has been activated, is to resume the Playback of the simulation.    The associated status text is displayed along with the buttons. The status text indicates whether the simulation is running, whether Pause is activated at that precise moment or whether a step is being loaded.   Note: The buttons are only intended for controlling steps. It is not possible to use it to influence audio files contained in a step. If you do not wish to listen to an audio file, you can click on the step to move on.   ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_F6DC6642D2B2D385" title="Key Functions"><![CDATA[Key Functions Key Functions  Using the key functions, you can control the Trainer via the keyboard. These correspond to the button functionality.The key functions can be used for Demo mode and Concurrent mode, as it is possible to manipulate the sequence of events in these modes. The following keys are assigned by default to their respective functions:   Function  Key   Play  Space   Pause  Space   Stop      Back  Left   Next  Right   Feedback  Ctrl + F1   If other key functions are in use, then you can learn about this from the author of the simulation or your administrator. ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_4B0DA5AB4717D786" title="Progress Display"><![CDATA[Progress Display Progress Display  The Progress display provides an overview of the simulation and displays its history during playback.  The individual steps are shown as small buttons in the Progress display. These buttons are arranged on a bar showing how the simulation is progressing by changing the color of the different sections of the bar. If a step has been displayed, the status of the associated button changes.The title of the simulation and the name of the current step are displayed beneath the Progress display. You can use the buttons to jump between the individual steps and view a section of your choice. Placing the cursor over a button displays the name of the step beneath the Progress display. That makes it easier for you to find and select a step. ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_36B3F5EFB29C5B93" title="Orientation of the Trainer Bar
"><![CDATA[Orientation of the Trainer Bar
 Orientation of the Trainer Bar   You can alter the position of the Trainer bar to customize it for playing back a simulation. You can change this setting at any time. It is advisable to pause the mode first before switching states. The following states are available: Orientation The orientation allows the Trainer bar to be positioned accordingly in the screen area.   Bar at the top    Bar at the bottom    By changing the orientation, you can set up the Trainer bar in such a way that it does not obstruct your view of the simulation and can be accessed at any time. ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_ED594D45157978A7" title="Simulations Containing Audio"><![CDATA[Simulations Containing Audio Simulations Containing Audio  Simulations can contain audio files giving you additional information about the content. To listen to these files you should switch on the sound and connect a loudspeaker or headphones.You can adjust and also deactivate the sound using the volume settings. This is possible both for audio files as well as bubble audio effects. As audio files typically contain greater quantities of data, simulations and their associated steps may require more time to load than without audio.   Note:  Control of the Trainer bar is only envisaged for the steps. It is not possible to use it to influence audio files contained in a step. If you do not want to listen to an audio file, you can click on the step to move on. Playback of sound is not supported on the iPad.    ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_D54EE79E857D6EA5" title="Book Reader"><![CDATA[Book Reader Book Reader  The Book Reader is used for selecting book pages in a book as well as presenting these book pages.Books are the means by which you can obtain different learning material in many different forms on specific content. A book page can contain different objects and media on a specific topic, which you can work through at will. You can then scroll through to the next book page and so work through the topics step by step. Book pages are HTML pages on which the various objects are filed. These can be both different modes and documentation as well as different media formats or pure text. In the sections that follow, you will discover what the necessary requirements are, how the Book Reader is organized and how you can work with both it and the content it displays. The Book Reader and Trainer for playing back the modes are web-based applications and are therefore launched in the browser. Before you start to work through the learning content, ensure that the necessary settings are available in your browser. This will avoid errors in the way the learning content is displayed and runs. Consult your administrator if so required.  ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_25941754CA8FFD85" title="Book Reader Architecture and Components
"><![CDATA[Book Reader Architecture and Components
 Book Reader Architecture and Components   The Book Reader comprises the control bar and window for displaying the book page.   Orientation: This functions allows the position of the Book Reader bar to be manipulated. Start pageIf a book page is defined as the start page then you can call it directly using the Start page button. For example, the book page can contain introductory information or a table of contents. The button makes it easier for you to reach the start page directly at any time without having to resort to the book page selection. Buttons for scrolling within the book pages:The buttons allow you to scroll within the book pages. This is how you go forward or backward one book page at a time as well as how you use the external buttons to switch between chapters. Keyword searchThis button opens a dialog in which you can search the book's book pages for a specific book page. Progress displayThe progress display shows how many pages in a book have already been worked through. Moving the cursor over the progress display with the mouse shows you the number of book pages and current book page number. Book page selection:The book pages contained in the book can be selected by means of a dropdown list box, which displays an overview of the book pages. If the dropdown list box is closed, you can see the title of the chosen book page. Audio ControlsPlay/Stop AudioUsing this button allows you to start and stop background music or an audio commentary on a book page.On/Off AudioThis button allows you to activate and deactivate the page sound for a book.Volume:This function allows you to control or deactivate audio file volume and bubble effects. Clicking on the button opens a selection menu from which the volume can be controlled and the sound deactivated by means of a selection field. Close:The Close button is used to close the Book Reader . Window for displaying the book page:The chosen book page is displayed below the Book Reader control bar. You can now open the modes or documents, view a media file or work through some more content.    Note: Bear in mind that this Help describes the Book Reader's standard functions. These will not necessarily also be displayed in your Book Reader. The Book Reader's appearance and functions depend on the author's settings and may vary as a result.   ]]>
</page>

<page src="cdoc!CD_EF1BE15CEDFDD2BC" title="Keyword Search"><![CDATA[Keyword Search Keyword Search  The Book Reader allows you to search for a specific book page or content. Selecting the Search button opens the search dialog.You can enter a search word in this dialog or select a keyword from the list. You will then be shown the associated book pages. Now select a book page from the Hits field and click on the View button to display the book page.   Note: Keywords are only offered to you on the search dialog if they were defined by the author.   ]]>
</page>

<page src="cdoc!CD_28DD568C8688009D" title="Browser Requirements"><![CDATA[Browser Requirements Browser Requirements  The following requirements are to be considered to ensure an error-free use of the Trainer, Library and Book Reader functionalities, thus ensuring that contents are played back successfully.   Browser  Version  Operating system   Internet Explorer  7.0 – 11.0  Windows Vista, Windows 7 or Windows 8   Firefox  17.0.9 ESR - 27.0  Windows Vista, Windows 7, Windows 8 or Mac OS X 10.5.x   Safari  4.0 – 5.1  Windows Vista, Windows 7, Windows 8, Mac OS X 10.5.x   Supported mobile platforms Content playback has been tested for the system built-in browsers of the following mobile device platforms. Keep in mind, that playback on mobile devices usually requires an online connection to published contents (Content Management Platform or shared network storage).   Platform  OS version  Browser   Apple iOS  6, 7  Safari Mobile   Google Android  4.1.2  Stock Browser (AOSP) (with deactivated Desktop View)   Windows Mobile  8  Internet Explorer 10   ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_BA8CCDB2E59AA6B4" title="Settings for Internet Explorer"><![CDATA[Settings for Internet Explorer Settings for Internet Explorer  To enjoy a flawless experience of the Trainer, Library and Book Reader functions, you may have to enable additional security settings in Internet Explorer.  Note that your configuration requirements are highly dependent on the location you are playing your contents from. This is due to the zone model in Internet Explorer (see the next chapter for more details). However, all functions will run almost perfectly using the Internet Explorer default settings. ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_280B109C2ED57186" title="Basic Setup"><![CDATA[Basic Setup Basic Setup   Note: The settings configuration as handled in this chapter is based on the assumption that you use Internet Explorer's default settings and default security levels. If you use a custom security level, read the chapter  Custom Setup (Link->cdoc!CD_1606123861F2B387.htm)  to ensure your settings match the requirements.       Playback of contents located on the Internet/intranet  To apply Internet Explorer Security Settings, open Internet Explorer and navigate to the Internet Options command in the Tools menu. Click on the Tab Security and select Local Intranet or Internet, depending on where your contents are located. Click on Custom level... to open the Security Settings dialog. Enable the settings shown below.  Contents located on your intranet (Default security level: Medium-low)   Section/Setting  Set to  Why?   ActiveX controls and plug-ins         Display video and animation on a webpage that does not use external media player  Enable  Playback videos and animations embedded in book pages and quizzes directly with the browser, without loading an installed media player.    Contents located on the Internet (Default security level: Medium-high)   Section/Setting  Set to  Why?   ActiveX controls and plug-ins         Display video and animation on a webpage that does not use external media player  Enable  Playback videos and animations embedded in book pages and quizzes directly with the browser, without loading an installed media player.   Miscellaneous         Allow script-initiated windows without size or position constraints  Enable  Display simulation modes in Trainer and book pages in Book Reader with correctly positioned control elements.   Allow websites to open windows without address or status bars  Enable  Display the frameless top-most-window of the Concurrent Mode.      Playback of local contents If your contents are stored on a local hard drive or if your contents were delivered on a CD/DVD, you have to allow active contents to be run locally.  Open Internet Explorer and navigate to the Internet Options command in the Tools menu. Click on the Advanced tab and scroll to the Security section. Enable the settings as described in the following table.    Section/Setting  Why?   Allow active content to run in files on My Computer*  Playback contents from your local hard drive(s). This is especially important if you want to preview your authored contents from Authoring Environment or Process Recorder.   Allow active content from CDs to run on My Computer*  Playback published contents on CD/DVD.     Common settings  Configure Internet Explorer's pop-up blockerThe pop-up blocker needs to be deactivated to display simulations in the Trainer. This option can be accessed using the Tools -&gt; Pop-up blocker menu.Alternatively, you can input the corresponding URL in the pages that are enabled for pop-ups, in the Pop-up blocker settings. Print the stop pageTo print the stop page of the Trainer correctly you have to allow background elements to be printed. You will find the relevant settings as follows:  Internet Explorer 7:Go to Tools -&gt; Internet options and click the Advanced tab.Scroll down to the Printing section. Activate the setting Print background colors and images. Internet Explorer 8 and higher:Press the key ALT to display the menu bar. Select File &gt; Page Setup and activate the setting Print background colors and images.    ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_1606123861F2B387" title="Custom Setup"><![CDATA[Custom Setup Custom Setup Using a custom configuration hat has been modified by you or your company’s network policy might result in problems when playing back contents. Check that your settings match the following table.    Tip  Note the dependencies given to different content types and their necessary settings. Ensure that you configure the security settings for the correct zone (where your contents are located).     How to apply Settings  To apply necessary playback settings, open Internet Explorer and navigate to the Internet Options command in the Tools menu. Click on the according tab and apply settings as given in the table below.    For Security Settings  In Tab Security Settings select Local Intranet or Internet, depending on where your contents are located. Click on Custom level... to open the Security Settings dialog. Apply settings as given in the table below.    Settings overview To avoid display errors, column headers are displayed with a numeric icon that represents one of the following functions/content types:num. 1 - Librarynum. 2 - demo, test and practice modenum. 3 - concurrent modenum. 4 - book pagesnum. 5 - quizzes     Tab  Section/Setting  Set to  num. 1  num. 2  num. 3  num. 4  num. 5   General                           Tabs -&gt; Settings                        Always open pop-ups in a new window(When a pop-up is encountered)  Enable                 Security                         ActiveX controls and plug-ins                      Binary and script behavior  Enable              Display video and animation on a webpage that does not use external media player  Enable                  Miscellaneous                        Allow script-initiated windows without size or position constraints  Enable                  Allow websites to open windows without address or status bars  Enable                  Submit non-encrypted form data  Enable                 Scripting                        Active scripting  Enable             Advanced                           Multimedia                        Play sounds in webpages  Enable                 ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_744C16C91A265ABE" title="Notes to Internet Explorer versions"><![CDATA[Notes to Internet Explorer versions Notes to Internet Explorer versions  Internet Explorer 8  Using Internet Explorer 8 you have to activate the Protected Mode for your Intranet Zone to gain full playback functionality for contents played back from Intranet Zone.  Ensure to deactivate the standard use of Compatibility Mode to avoid display problems. To do so, open Tools &gt; Compatibility View Settings and deselect one or both of the following parameters, depending on your location you are playing back contents from.   Display all websites in Compatibility Mode Display intranet sites in Compatibility View     Internet Explorer 9  In Internet Explorer 9, turn off the Protected Mode for the network zone that is the source of the contents. This ensures correct window handling for links that open content in a new window. Not doing so might result in the window being opened in full screen mode, without the possibility to close the simulation before it is finished.  Ensure to deactivate the standard use of Compatibility Mode to avoid display problems. To do so, open Tools &gt; Compatibility View Settings (press ALT to display the toolbar) and deselect one or both of the following parameters, depending on your location you are playing back contents from.   Display all websites in Compatibility Mode Display intranet sites in Compatibility View     Internet Explorer 11  With Internet Explorer 11 the concurrent mode will not run natively in top most window anymore. To fix this issue you will have to activate Internet Explorer's Enterprise Mode. Read more about the Enterprise Mode in the  Internet Explorer 11 Deployment Guide (Link->http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/library/dn640687.aspx) .    ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_37056C831730E6B1" title="Internet Explorer’s zone model"><![CDATA[Internet Explorer’s zone model Internet Explorer’s zone model  Security settings are divided into specific zones in Internet Explorer. Internet Explorer distinguishes between four zones: Internet, Local Intranet, Trusted sites and Restricted sites. It is possible to configure the settings in detail for the permitted actions within each zone. In corporate networks, it is generally the administrator who configures these settings in accordance with the company policy. Otherwise, users may also define the settings themselves. A document is assigned to a specific zone based on two characteristics:   Path / URL for documents – The paths/URLs for documents can be configured in Internet Explorer for each of the four zones (Internet, Local Intranet, Trusted sites and Restricted sites). All other paths/URLs are automatically allocated to the zone Internet.    The file's source (when downloading via the Windows file system) - When a document is downloaded from an external source, the zone that the file was in upon downloading is automatically allocated to the file. In this case, Internet Explorer’s security settings for the zone (ZoneID) detected in the file will apply.      Attention: To ensure that everything runs smoothly, it is recommended that you verify that the security zone settings for the server as well as for the published contents and the Trainer on the end user's side allow the contents to be played back without any problems.   ]]>
</page>
<page src="cdoc!CD_10F43626FBB2F4BC" title="Settings for Mozilla Firefox"><![CDATA[Settings for Mozilla Firefox Settings for Mozilla Firefox  The following settings are required for a flawless playback experience in Mozilla Firefox.  Changes in the settings dialogSelect the Settings item in the Tools menu in the open browser. Now go to the Content item in the settings dialog to see the required options.    Setting  Set to   Block pop-up windows  Deactivate   Activate JavaScript  Activate   Advanced JavaScript settings  Click on the Advanced button to open Advanced JavaScript settings. Activate the following options:   Position window before or after other windows    Hide status bar    Change status bar text         Settings using about:configAdditional browser configuration settings are available to you in Firefox. You can access these settings by entering about:config in the address bar and confirming with Enter.Enter setting name into Search field. A setting can be activated by double-clicking on it. It is then displayed in bold text and the value true is set.The following settings are to be set to the value true:    Setting  What does it do?   dom.allow_scripts_to_close_windows   This setting allows the browser windows to be closed.   signed.applets.codebase_principal_support  This setting displays browser windows in fullscreen mode.   dom.disable_window_open_feature.resizable  This setting prevents the size of an open browser window from being changed.   security.fileuri.strict_origin_policy  This setting allows links to be executed if an HTML page is launched from a local drive.         Printing the stop pageTo print the stop page of the Trainer correctly you have to allow the print of background elements. Activate the setting Print background (Colors and Images) which is to be find within the page setup dialog under File -&gt; Page setup.      Note:  Caused by the settings that have been activated, you will face a security message when starting the Library or a content in the Trainer. Confirm this message with Allow. Activate the option Remember this decision so that the security message will not be displayed each time the Library starts. The default bubble audio effects in simulations and in the Book Reader actions are in WAV format. A Windows Media Player plugin is required in order to be able to play back the files in Firefox.You will find further information on the subject at:  https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/browse/type:7 (Link->https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/browse/type:7)      ]]>
</page>

</Contents>